[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [6, 4, 3, 1], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": [""], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084"], "type": "advance", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "How many strings are there?", "options": [6, 3, 2, 5], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "type": "advance", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081+20=2a\u2081", "-T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "-T\u2081+20=2a\u2081", "+T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "+T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string", "T\u2083: Tension in white string", "N\u2081: Normal between yellow block and Big blockblue block and Big block", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 downwards", "T\u2081 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081+20=2a\u2081", "-T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "-T\u2081+20=2a\u2081", "+T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, "], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: 20", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081-30=0", "-N\u2081-30=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "+N\u2081-30=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string", "T\u2083: Tension in white string", "N\u2081: Normal between yellow block and Big blockblue block and Big block", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 2 due to B?", "options": ["N1 perpendicular up", "N1 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "type": "advance", "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "answer": 2}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 rightwards", "T\u2081 leftwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 rightwards", "T\u2082 leftwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 3, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2081-30=0", "-N\u2081-30=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "+T\u2081-T\u2082=3a\u2082", "-T\u2081-T\u2082=3a\u2082", "-T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "-T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string", "T\u2083: Tension in white string", "N\u2081: Normal between yellow block and Big blockblue block and Big block", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "+T\u2081-T\u2082=3a\u2082", "-T\u2081-T\u2082=3a\u2082", "-T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N1, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2081, "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2082-40=0", "-N\u2082-40=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "+N\u2082-40=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string", "T\u2083: Tension in white string", "N\u2081: Normal between yellow block and Big blockblue block and Big block", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 3 due to B?", "options": ["N2 perpendicular up", "N2 perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "type": "advance", "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for blue block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "answer": 2}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on blue block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 rightwards", "T\u2082 leftwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on blue block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2083 leftwards", "T\u2083 rightwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 3, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2082, "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the y-direction", "options": ["+N\u2082-40=0", "-N\u2082-40=0"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N2, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: T\u2083, ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2082, "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "+T\u2082-T\u2083=4a\u2083", "-T\u2082-T\u2083=4a\u2083", "-T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "-T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string", "T\u2083: Tension in white string", "N\u2081: Normal between yellow block and Big blockblue block and Big block", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the x-direction", "options": ["+T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "+T\u2082-T\u2083=4a\u2083", "-T\u2082-T\u2083=4a\u2083", "-T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: N2, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: T\u2083, ", "Leftward Forces: T\u2082, "], "showfcheading": ["Blue block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of green block in the y-direction", "options": ["+50+T\u2083=5a\u2084", "+50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "-50+T\u2083=5a\u2084", "-50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": -300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "+50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string", "T\u2082: Tension in red string", "T\u2083: Tension in white string", "N\u2081: Normal between yellow block and Big blockblue block and Big block", "N\u2081: Normal between "], "showfcheading": ["Green block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for green block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Green block"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on green block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2083 downwards", "T\u2083 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Green block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of green block in the y-direction", "options": ["+50+T\u2083=5a\u2084", "+50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "-50+T\u2083=5a\u2084", "-50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083"], "type": "advance", "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: T\u2083, ", "Downward Forces: 50", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Green block"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081-a\u2082=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "-a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["a\u2081: acceleration of red block in y-direction", "a\u2082y: acceleration of yellow block in y-direction", "a\u2082: acceleration of yellow block in x-direction", "a\u2083y: acceleration of blue block in y-direction", "a\u2083: acceleration of blue block in x-direction", "a\u2084: acceleration of green block in y-direction", "a\u2085y: acceleration of second pulley in y-direction", "a\u2085x: acceleration of second pulley in x-direction"], "showfcheading": ["Pink string"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the pink string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "type": "advance", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": ["Pink string"], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string due to red block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2081", "-a\u2081"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"], "showfcheading": ["Pink string"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for pink string due to yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"], "showfcheading": ["Pink string"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081-a\u2082=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084"], "showfc": ["l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant", "l\u2081'' = -a\u2081", "l\u2082'' = +a\u2082"], "showfcheading": ["Pink string"], "tobeshown": 0, "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "type": "advance"}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["a\u2081: acceleration of red block in y-direction", "a\u2082y: acceleration of yellow block in y-direction", "a\u2082: acceleration of yellow block in x-direction", "a\u2083y: acceleration of blue block in y-direction", "a\u2083: acceleration of blue block in x-direction", "a\u2084: acceleration of green block in y-direction", "a\u2085y: acceleration of second pulley in y-direction", "a\u2085x: acceleration of second pulley in x-direction"], "showfcheading": ["Red string"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string due to yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["l\u2081 = constant"], "showfcheading": ["Red string"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string due to blue block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["l\u2081 = constant"], "showfcheading": ["Red string"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0"], "showfc": ["l\u2081 = constant", "l\u2081'' = -a\u2082 +a\u2083"], "showfcheading": ["Red string"], "tobeshown": 0, "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "type": "advance"}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for white string?", "options": ["+a\u2083+a\u2084=0", "+a\u2083-a\u2084=0", "-a\u2083+a\u2084=0", "-a\u2083-a\u2084=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "-a\u2083+a\u2084=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["a\u2081: acceleration of red block in y-direction", "a\u2082y: acceleration of yellow block in y-direction", "a\u2082: acceleration of yellow block in x-direction", "a\u2083y: acceleration of blue block in y-direction", "a\u2083: acceleration of blue block in x-direction", "a\u2084: acceleration of green block in y-direction", "a\u2085y: acceleration of second pulley in y-direction", "a\u2085x: acceleration of second pulley in x-direction"], "showfcheading": ["White string"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the white string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": [], "showfcheading": ["White string"], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for white string due to blue block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"], "showfcheading": ["White string"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for white string due to green block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2084", "-a\u2084"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 5, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "type": "advance", "showfc": ["l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant"], "showfcheading": ["White string"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for white string?", "options": ["+a\u2083+a\u2084=0", "+a\u2083-a\u2084=0", "-a\u2083+a\u2084=0", "-a\u2083-a\u2084=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0"], "showfc": ["l\u2081 + l\u2082 = constant", "l\u2081'' = -a\u2083", "l\u2082'' = +a\u2084"], "showfcheading": ["White string"], "tobeshown": 0, "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "White string: -a\u2083+a\u2084=0"], "type": "advance"}]}, {"stepName": "Final Answers", "stepNumber": 4, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What are the final accelerations, tensions and normal reactions?", "options": ["a\u2081= 17.12, a\u2082= 30.0, a\u2083= 235.74, a\u2084= -17.12, T\u2081= 61.42, T\u2082= 14.98, T\u2083= 14.98, N\u2081= 170.03, N\u2082= 80.0", "a\u2081= 2.14, a\u2082= 2.14, a\u2083= 2.14, a\u2084= -2.14, T\u2081= 24.29, T\u2082= 30.71, T\u2083= 39.29, N\u2081= 30.0, N\u2082= 40.0", "a\u2081= 14.98, a\u2082= 14.98, a\u2083= 30.71, a\u2084= 30.0, T\u2081= 145.74, T\u2082= -2.14, T\u2083= 120.0, N\u2081= 196.45, N\u2082= 12.84", "a\u2081= 157.16, a\u2082= 180.0, a\u2083= -19.26, a\u2084= 8.56, T\u2081= 194.32, T\u2082= 2.14, T\u2083= 120.0, N\u2081= 307.1, N\u2082= 4.28"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "finalanswer", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "White string: -a\u2083+a\u2084=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 1, "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, T\u2083, ", "Red block: +T\u2081-20=2a\u2081", "Yellow block: +N\u2081-30=0", "Yellow block: -T\u2081+T\u2082=3a\u2082", "Blue block: +N\u2082-40=0", "Blue block: -T\u2082+T\u2083=4a\u2083", "Green block: +50-T\u2083=5a\u2084", "Pink string: -a\u2081+a\u2082=0", "Red string: -a\u2082+a\u2083=0", "White string: -a\u2083+a\u2084=0", "Final Answers: a\u2081= 2.14, a\u2082= 2.14, a\u2083= 2.14, a\u2084= -2.14, T\u2081= 24.29, T\u2082= 30.71, T\u2083= 39.29, N\u2081= 30.0, N\u2082= 40.0"]}]}]